I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
"Fishing Hole"
Damn...
"Live 19
'Blues'"
He's probably walking Beck.
For two days?
He hasn't contacted you...
Maybe...
Hey, Grandma, aren't you worried?!
No thanks...
Looks like Lucille's gone, too.
That guy...
He wants to go to Kyoto...
Leon-san seems quite fond of Japan.
Yeah...I heard he was
influenced by his uncle.
Oh?
His uncle took him in when
he was little, and raised him.
Seems his uncle's wife was Japanese.
Leon-san has overcome much
in order to succeed, I guess.
I don't know the details,
but I hear he's got the blood
of five continents in his veins-
including Asian, Anglo-Saxon and African.
Five?
Of course, it's just a rumor.
-I find him a little scary.
-Yeah...
Hi, Boss...
Well, I'm here myself.
I guess everyone is shopping
in Akihabara right now.
That man?
That's fine.
I beat the hell outta him.
He won't even think
of running away from us.
Okay, 10 o'clock. Tokyo Station?
I'll pick you up on time, Boss.
Fucking blood on my...I can't believe
this muthafucker hit me in the head!
I'll kill you, little fucker!
Damn it! You really pissed me off!
Mister Sykes...
Do you know the guy
called John Lee Davis?
He called you at the office.
He's in Japan right now as
a backup band for a soul singer.
Oh...I haven't seen him for three years...
Oh?
He, John Lee Davis, is my uncle.
He must have gotten to know Mr. Sykes'
coming to Japan, by TV or something.
Cross Road? That's classic...
Is your uncle there at that restaurant?
Yeah. He always goes there
when he visits Japan.
I see. Anyway Boss,
why do we wanna bring him?
Punk ass never does anything, anywhere.
I told him that we found the Lucille,
and that a Japanese musician stole it.
And now, he wants to see him.
Isn't it going to be too much trouble?
How's that dog?
Hmph...He'll never take to me.
The blues...
Sounds like Robert Johnson...
Surprising...
Money mad boss, Leon Sykes,
talk about Robert Johnson?
Hey...Leon!
Come on...What are you putting
on that dreadful face for?
I wouldn't sue you for money
like your dad did.
Come on, Leon. This is
your Uncle John Lee Davis!
John...
Leon...
Is that the Japanese?
Yeah. Ryusuke Minami.
The fucked up punk
who used a picture of Lucille
for the album jacket that was released
by an Indies label in Chicago.
Say somethin'!
I'm gonna go wash my hands.
Yeah...
I was listening to you play, earlier.
Hey, brat...You still alive?
You might be Mr. John Lee Davis?
Good...Now what about this?
That's from the gigs
in San Francisco, 1964.
Hey...When were you born?
Let me play with Mr. Davis, for my last...
Can you play with hands like that?
Fortunately...my left hand is fine.
Yeah...
The blues...It ain't all that bad.
Not good for business.
Sure ain't gonna make us rich.
Your guitar sound
reminds me of Sonny Boy.
Is that right?
Sonny Boy is my master.
Jesus Christ! Then what about Lucille?
Sonny Boy had no one to depend on...
I was the only one who would
take Lucille on, after him.
But I don't have what
it takes to own Lucille.
So if the real Blues Man for Lucille
showed up, I'd've handed it over to him.
You are the real Blues Man.
I gave up the music scene once...
I left Lucille to Leon, since then.
Mr. John Lee Davis, it was
a great honor to play with you.
Thank you.
Doitashimashite.
("You're welcome")
You want a cigarette?
No, thanks.
Leon, he is real.
I've never seen any Japanese
who could express Blues that good.
And on top of that, he's really young.
Erica Blige has been murdered,
and I heard rumor that you are the suspect.
Erica had been critical of the RJ label.
Leon...Would you kill
people for money, like this?
He's too good to kill.
Uncle...Even though you try to
live straight in this fucked up society...
chances are, you'll die a loser.
Most people die that way.
So I...
What a fucking cheesy fucked up music!
Ouch!
It's been four days since
Ryusuke-kun disappeared.
Yeah...
Maybe we should report it to the police.
It's almost time for our performance.
-I'll have the lady at the
fishing hole make a report.
-Hey!
-Take a look at this! Hey!
-Huh? Chiba-kun!
Uh...Has something happened?
What...You two don't know about it?
Ta-da!
"Maho Minami"
Ma...ho?
"Maho Minami-Sparkling 16-year-old"
Maho...Minami...
Sixteen...
"The moment the scent...
of excitement explodes."
She might well become
"The moment the scent...
of excitement explodes."
An overnight sensation.
"The moment the scent...
of excitement explodes."
There are guys like you two all over
the nation, who'll be stuck on her.
I-I'm not stuck on her!
You can have it. See you!
What are the two of you stuck on?
Uh, just a book that explains how to
conquer computer games...I guess...
Yeah, yeah...
Oh?
Didn't you hear about it
from Maho, Koyuki?
I haven't seen her lately.
She seems busy...
Oh, Saku-chan, you have a nosebleed.
Ah!
Oh, Taira-kun! What's up?
What?!
-What's the matter, Chiba-kun?!
-Yeah! I'll be right there!!
-Oh...Chiba-kun!
Hey! Ryusuke!
Yo...
He says he was out walking Beck.
Why are you all bandaged up?
Ryusuke-kun...Are you all right?
Where were you?
Where the heck are Beck and Lucille?!
Well...Money and women...
Don't ask awkward questions, will you?
W-W-Women?
Money?
Anyway...Beck and Lucille
won't be coming back.
-I'll go and talk to him.
-See you later.
Yeah...
Really, man...What were you doing?
-Shut up, will you?
-Come on...Be nice.
Ryusuke-kun...
-It tastes a little different...
-Yeah...
Boy, our boss is really...
In other words...I wasn't worth killing.
Yeah...That's right. I do kill for money.
But I don't just murder people
for no reason.
Now get the fuck outta here!
Can someone like me create music
that will move people?
What are you saying?!
He's right! You're lucky to be alive!
Hey, Saku! Look at this!!
"Pro-Am Welcome Auditions!!"
This would be a great chance!
Ohh...Auditions!?
Let's tell Ryusuke-kun about it.
Good idea!
I don't know about that...
-Huh?
-Uh...
Those auditions were over two months ago.
Huh? No way...
Besides, bands prepare a whole year
for that Grateful Sound event.
A-And you are?
For your information,
the band that was chosen
was a promising newcomer called
"La Majistol" on the Ran label.
Ran...
-In other words...
The contest was rigged.
-Uh, ma'am...
-Ma'am?!
-This fishing hole is closed today.
Huh?
Y-Y-Y-You...Are you the boy who sang
with Dying Breed in that Jim Walsh movie?
Yes. I am...
This...This is you guys, right?
Yes...
Mongolian Chop Squad is the
name of our band in America.
I did it! I finally found you!
I wasn't mistaken.
My deductions were right,
after all! This is great!!
Hey! Didn't I tell you
not to let customers in?!
She's not a customer...
I guess she is...but not really...
-That lady heard our American CD
and used it to find us.
-Eeek! I hooked something!
What should I do?!
-That lady?
-Somebody, help!
Hm...Metal Glue...
"Wao Sato-Metal Glue, Inc."
-Wa...o...Sato?
-Phew! It smells fishy...
"Wao Sato-Metal Glue, Inc."
-Here. Give it to me, please.
-Huh? Huh? What should I do?
-Hello?
-Hey, Ray...What the fuck're you doing?
Oh! I'm sorry, I'm kinda busy...
Just a sec...
Hey! Koyuki...
Huh? What is it?
Hello?
Koyuki?
Ryusuke-kun's back safely.
He was probably over at some girl's.
Never mind that...
There's a sneak preview of the
Dying Breed tour movie today!
What?! The Dying Breed movie?!
Hello?
Koyuki, you want to see it with me?
-Yeah!
-Mm...
-I gotta go...
-Yes! Go on!!
Saku...
Okay! Give this to Ryusuke-kun, will you?!
How nice...
He's enjoying his youth.
You're late!
I just got a call from Yoshito.
He said he wanted to
see the movie too, so...
Being with two guys...
isn't very good for Maho's future.
Yoshito-kun, you want
to look at the program?
I never read it before a movie.
Oh...
On the stage, they are perfect.
They're flawless.
Yes they are...And maybe not,
depending on your point of view.
Ahem. Excuse me...
Everybody has a life, a daily life.
There's no exception; they do.
Conflict with their agent?
It's none of our business!
Of course, Eddy. These guys
are the next big thing in Japan.
If we like them at the rehearsal,
yeah, we could play with them.
Belle Ame...It means
"beautiful spirit" in French.
Bugger off. Hit the road.
-Jim, give me that!
-After all, Eddy is just a guy.
-Hey! They're waiting for us.
-Why are you saying this now? Shit!
-But, that makes Dying Breed appealing.
-What shall we do? That's irresponsible.
Hey Jim! What are you filming!?
-On top of that, Matt is wild.
Like a river flowing,
inspiration always flows from my mind.
-Hey! Dancing, dancing...Party man...
-Oh! He's a funny guy.
-Happy birthday to you...
Sometimes, there comes a special day,
while they're on tour.
It's a beautiful scene.
Tokyo...a city of noise
and chaos. Techno-city.
Come on!
They had a live here, as well.
In the evening, with the shining moon...
They met a boy. It was
a very special event.
I felt like something great...
...was about to happen.
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
That Sato lady was funny, wasn't she?
"Live 20
'Grateful Sound'”
Next episode: Grateful Sound!
Will Beck be able to perform?